Now that was when we had two classes namely receiving a gift or not receiving a gift.
さて2つのクラスがあり ギフトを受けられるクラスと 受けられないクラスです
What happens if we have more classes? Let's take a look.
クラスがもっと多かったら どうなるでしょう  見てみましょう
So we have a similar problem.
同じような問題が生じます
We still have three doors.
やはり3つのドアがあります
And this problem is still not the Monty Hall problem.
この問題はモンティホール問題ではありません
Behind each door there can be an animal,
それぞれのドアの後ろには動物がいます
and the animal can be of three types.
3種類の動物です
It can be a duck, it can be a beaver,
アヒルかもしれず ビーバーかもしれず
or it can be a walrus.
セイウチかもしれません
So let's look at this table of probabilities.
この確率表を見てみましょう
According to the first column on the table,
表の最初の列に従って
behind the first door,
最初のドアの後ろに
the probability of finding a duck is 0.7,
アヒルがいる確率は0.7です
the probability of finding a beaver is 0.2,
ビーバーがいる確率は0.2
and the probability of finding a walrus is 0.1.
セイウチがいる確率は0.1です
Notice that the numbers in each column need to add to
各列の数の合計は1である必要があります
one because there is some animal behind door one.
ドア1の後ろには どれかの動物が必ずいるからです
The numbers in the rows do not need to add to one as you can see.
見てのとおり 行の数の合計は1である必要はありません
It could easly be that we have a duck behind every door and that's okay.
どのドアの後ろにもアヒルがいるかもしれません  それはかまいません
So let's look at a sample scenario.
では サンプルシナリオを見てみましょう
Let's say we have our three doors,
3つのドアがあり
and behind the first door, there's a duck,
最初のドアの後ろにはアヒルがいます
behind the second door there's a walrus,
2番目のドアの後ろにはセイウチがいます
and behind the third door there's also a walrus.
3番目のドアの後ろには やはりセイウチがいます
Recall that the probabilities are again by the table.
確率表を思い出してください
So a duck behind the first door is 0.7 likely,
最初のドアの後ろにアヒルがいる確率は0.7
a walrus behind the second door is 0.3 likely,
2番目のドアの後ろにセイウチがいる確率は0.3
and a walrus behind the third door is 0.4 likely.
3番目のドアの後ろにセイウチがいる確率は0.4です
So the probability of obtaining this three animals is the product of
この3種類の動物が当たる確率は
the probabilities of the three events since they are independent events,
3回のイベントの確率の積です  独立したイベントだからです
which in this case it's 0.084.
この場合0.084になります
And as we learn,
学んだように
that cross entropy here is given by
ここでのクロスエントロピーは
the sums of the negatives of the logarithms of the probabilities.
確率の対数のマイナスの和によって与えられます
So the first one is negative logarithm of 0.7.
最初は0.7のマイナス対数です
The second one is negative logarithm of 0.3.
2番目は0.3のマイナス対数です
And the third one is negative logarithm of 0.4.
3番目は0.4のマイナス対数です
The Cross entropy's and the sum of these three which is actually 2.48.
クロスエントロピーとこの3つの和は実際には2.48です
But we want a formula, so let's put some variables here.
しかし 必要なのは式なので いくつかの変数を入れてみましょう
So P11 is the probability of finding a duck behind door one.
P11はドア1の後ろにアヒルがいる確率です
P12 is the probability of finding a duck behind door two etc.
P12はドア2の後ろにアヒルがいる確率です
And let's have the indicator variables Y1j D1 if there's
ドアjの後ろにアヒルがいる場合の指標変数は
a duck behind door J. Y2j B1 if there's a beaver behind door J,
Y1j=1です ドアjの後ろにビーバーがいる場合は Y2j=1です
and Y3j B1 if there's a walrus behind door J.
ドアjの後ろにセイウチがいる場合はY3j=1です
And these variables are zero otherwise.
そうでない場合 これらの変数はゼロです
And so, the formula for the cross entropy is
クロスエントロピーの式は
simply the negative of the summation from i_ equals_ one to n,
i=1からnまでの加算と
up to summation from y_ equals_ j to m of Yij_ times_ the logarithm of Pij.
j=1からmまでの加算にYijとPijを掛けたもののマイナスです
In this case, m is a number of classes.
この場合 mはクラスの数です
This formula works because Yij being zero one,
この式が機能するのはYijがゼロか1であるため
makes sure that we're only adding the logarithms
実際に発生したイベントの確率の
of the probabilities of the events that actually have occurred.
対数を加算するだけだからです
And voila, this is the formula for the cross entropy in more classes.
ほら これがより多くのクラスのクロスエントロピーの式です
Now I'm going to leave this equestion.
この問題は置いておきましょう
Given that we have a formula for cross entropy for two classes and one for m classes.
2つのクラスとmクラスのクロスエントロピーの式が得られました
These formulas look different but are they the same for m_ equals_ two?
これらの式は違うように見えますが m=2の場合は同じでしょうか
Obviously the answer is yes,
当然 答えはイエスです
but it's a cool exercise to actually write them down and
実際にこれらを書き留めて
convince yourself that they are actually the same.
実際に同じかどうか確認してみると 良い練習になります